hoverspot.com 2006-12-10

# HoverSpot.com Privacy Policy

---  
  
|  |   |  |   
---|---|---|---  
---  
| 

**My Hover Home**   

|  | 

Search Members

| 

| 

Invite

| 

| 

| 

| 

Rate

| 

| 

Blog

| 

| 

Games

| 

| 

Points

| 

| 

Music

| 

| 

Sign Up

|  |   

**HoverSpot Privacy Policy**

**Effective December 21, 2005:**

**About HoverSpot.** HoverSpot (we or our) is an online network (the "Site") that allows members to express themselves by publishing (hereinafter "posting" ) a personal profile web page, photos, blogs, and by posting comments on the web pages, photos and blogs of other members. The HoverSpot ("HoverSpot") service (the "Service") is operated by Centrya, Inc. The Privacy of our members is extremely important to us. If you have any questions about this policy please contact us at http://www.hoverspot.com/contact.php. HoverSpot welcomes feedback on this document and policy.

The Service allows our members to link their personal profiles to those of members that they have accepted as buddies. Through the network of buddies our members can view each others' profiles and communicate with buddies on the service. The service allows members to share photos, post blogs and comments, and describe their interests. Based on elections made on their Hover Home Page(the Home Page), Members determine which personal information is displayed on their web page. 

By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of your personal information as described in this policy. If we make any significant changes to this policy, we will notify you by posting a notice of such changes on the HoverSpot login page. You should know: 

  1. We collect limited account information and store and maintain your account and all related content (including but not limited to profile information, pictures, comments and bog postings) on our servers. 
  2. We will never rent, sell or share information that personally identifies you for marketing purposes without your express permission. 
  3. You can update your account information, and related content and preferences at any time.

To comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, HoverSpot is only available to users who are at least 14 years old. If you are under 14, please do not use the Service. 

**Personal Information Collected by HoverSpot.** HoverSpot uses your personal information primarily to customize your experience using the Web site. The more information you volunteer, the better we can personalize HoverSpot�s products and services to match your needs and interests. To continue to provide our services, HoverSpot may display advertisements or other promotional information based on the information you have provided. HoverSpot may share general demographic information with advertisers and business partners (such as aggregated statistics about members' interests and occupations). But HoverSpot will never give advertisers access to your individual personal account information. Except as otherwise described in this privacy statement, HoverSpot will not disclose personal information to any third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary: 

  1. to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by HoverSpot.com, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; 
  2. to enforce the HoverSpot.com Terms of Use Agreement or to protect our rights; or 
  3. to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues (including, without limitation, the filtering of spam), (5) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the service. 

HoverSpot reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of HoverSpot or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest. For more information see the "Changes to This Privacy Policy" section below. 

**Account information.** When you register with HoverSpot, we will request some personal information, including your first and last name, a user name (which will be used for your email address) and password to create your account. Your password will be maintained on our system in an encrypted form. Just in case you forget your password, we also may ask you to choose a secret question and answer so that we can contact you to re-access your HoverSpot account. 

You may volunteer additional personal information at other times including, but not limited to, creating a Profile page, uploading personal pictures, or creating blogs. Any additional personal information that you submit to HoverSpot will be protected under the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. 

User information including members' pictures and first names are displayed to people in order to facilitate user interaction within the Service. Email addresses are used for the purposes of inviting new acquaintenances ("buddies") to join HoverSpot, to add users to members' buddy networks, and to send notifications related to the service. With the exception of inviting buddies, adding buddies, and notifications, a user's email address is not shared or displayed to people within a user's personal network. Users within a personal network communicate on HoverSpot with each other through the Service, without disclosing their email addresses. Users' full names are never directly revealed to other members. To facilitate searching and finding friends and acquaintances on the service, HoverSpot allows users to search for other members using first and last name, email address, and schools and/or companies where users may have attended or worked.

We may also use a user's email address to send updates, a newsletter or news regarding the service. Users may choose not to receive email of this type by changing their setting in the "Set your notifications" setting to "Do not send me notification emails" in the user "Account Settings."

From time to time, HoverSpot or a partner may sponsor a promotion, sweepstake or contest on HoverSpot. Users may be asked to provide personal information including name, email address or home address or to answer questions in order to participate. We may transfer personal information to certain ad partners that you have explicitly requested to receive information from. It will be clear at the point of collection who is collecting the personal information and whose privacy statement will apply.

**Browser Information.** Every time you visit a page on the Internet, your web browser sends specific information to the web site you are visiting. Our server logs automatically collect and store this information from your web browser, including your IP address, specific type of browser software, HoverSpot related cookies (see below), and the pages you visit at HoverSpot. This data is used to manage the website, track usage and improve the website services. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third-parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to members. User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes.

**Cookies.** A cookie is a small data file that is sent to your computer when you first visit a website. HoverSpot uses cookies to recognize you when you return to HoverSpot and to keep track of your username and password when you are signed in (so you don't have to re-sign in every time you visit a new page at HoverSpot). As with most website cookies, our cookies include an identification number that is unique to the computer you are using. This identifier helps us better understand our user base and how they are using our site and services. 

When you visit HoverSpot and create a HoverSpot account, we set and access cookies on your computer. We use cookies for a number of reasons, such as recognizing you when you visit the site and maintaining the security of your account. HoverSpot may share cookie information among its other services for the purpose of providing you a better experience. For example, you may use your HoverSpot account to access other HoverSpot services. We may also use the cookies to collect aggregated information about the use of HoverSpot to maintain, analyze and improve the service. 

We believe our cookies improve the quality of our services. If you prefer, however, you can reset your browser so that it refuses all cookies, or notifies you when a cookie is being sent. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set -- each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences -- however, you must enable cookies from HoverSpot in order to use most functions on the site Please note that HoverSpot allows 3rd party advertisers that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Advertisers' use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not the HoverSpot Privacy Policy.

**Log information.** When you use your HoverSpot account, we collect certain information (the same information that most web sites log when they are accessed). This information, contained in the "header" of your request to access the HoverSpot page, usually includes the browser type you used, your Internet Protocol address, and the date and time of day. In addition, we log the unique ID provided by our cookie and the URL of the last site you visited. 

As a basic matter, we need this information to help us provide our services to you. For example, we need to validate your identity in order to maintain the security of the Service. We also need to know what Internet Protocol address your query came from so we can send the appropriate pages back to you. 

In addition, we log this information for internal business purposes. For example, this log information helps us determine how well our services are working so we can continually improve the quality of HoverSpot. The log information is also important for security, audit, quality improvement, and other internal business purposes.

**Invitations and Other Communications to Non-members.** HoverSpot members can invite buddies to join the service by sending invitation emails via our automated invitation system. All invitations sent by HoverSpot's automated invitation system are initiated by a HoverSpot user. HoverSpot stores the email addresses that members provide so that the respondents may be added to the buddy list of the member sending the invitations, and also to send reminders of the invitations. HoverSpot does not sell these email addresses or use them to send any other communication besides invitations or invitation reminders (up to three (3) per email address). Recipients of invitations from HoverSpot may contact HoverSpot to request the removal of their information from our database. If a HoverSpot user does not change the displayed default message, the displayed default message will be sent. 

HoverSpot members may also store email addresses of people they know in their internal HoverSpot address book and may also choose to send invitations and other communications to those addresses.

You may prevent HoverSpot email invitations and other messages from being sent to any email address you control by going to [ http://www.hoverspot.com/removeme.php](http://www.hoverspot.com/removeme.php).

**Links.** HoverSpot contains links to sites, and is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on HoverSpot.

**Public Areas.** Please be aware that any information you voluntarily post to your profile page or to your blog can be accessed by anyone on the internet including individuals who are not members of the Service. Comments posted on photos and in other areas of the web site can be accessed by any member of the service. In order to protect your privacy comply with the HoverSpot Terms of Service and do not post personally identifiable information in you profile, blog, or photo comment section. Treat all information posted on any section of the site like information posted on a public bulletin board that could be accessed by anyone. 

**Adding Changing or Removing Information.** Members may modify login and personal information at any time by logging into their Hover Home Page and accessing features such as "Edit My Text" and "Account Settings."

**Third Party Advertising** Ads appearing on this Web site may be delivered to users by HoverSpot or one of our Web advertising partners. Our Web advertising partners may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad servers may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by HoverSpot and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

**Third Party Cookies.** In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. 

**Security.** HoverSpot member accounts are secured by member-created passwords HoverSpot takes precautions to insure that member account information is kept private. We use reasonable measures to protect member information that is stored within our database, and we restrict access to member information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our customer service personnel and technical staff. Please note that we cannot guarantee the security of member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time For any additional information about the security measures we use on HoverSpot, please contact us at http://www.hoverspot.com/contact.php.

**Children's Privacy.** HoverSpot is intended for use by people who are at least 14 years old, and we will not knowingly collect personal information from children under 14. 

We have designed our registration process to make it clear that you must be at least 14 years old to participate in the HoverSpot community (including activities such as creating a HoverSpot site, leaving comments on other HoverSpot sites, and emailing HoverSpot members through the HoverSpot.com website). 

**Note to Parents.** If you are the Parent or Legal Guardian of a child under 14 who has become a HoverSpot member and you would like his or her account deleted, please click here to send us an email.

As soon as we are able to verify your identity (and status as parent or legal guardian) we will immediately delete your child's account. You may also request to see a copy of any information that has been submitted by your child, prior to the account being deleted from our systems. 

For more information about the kinds of personally identifiable information collected by HoverSpot, how it is collected, and how it is used by HoverSpot, please review this Privacy Policy as well as the HoverSpot Terms of Use. 

For more information about protecting your child's privacy online, please visit the [ "Kidz Privacy"](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/edcams/kidzprivacy/index.html) website operated by the Federal Trade Commission. 

**Changes to This Privacy Policy.** From time to time we may make changes to our privacy policy If we make changes, we will post them on our site to make users aware of what the changes are so users will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we may disclose it. A User is bound by any minor changes to the policy when she or he uses the site after those changes have been posted If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify by posting a notice on our Web site for 30 days. 

**Other Privacy Related Issues.** We will do everything in our power to maintain your privacy and online security. Strong privacy and security, however, requires effort from both HoverSpot.com and its members. Please be sure to follow the advice listed above for protecting your HoverSpot account. The best way to protect your privacy is to protect your password; change your password often, and keep it secret, even from HoverSpot.com employees. 

**HoverSpot.com employees will never ask you for your password.**

**Contacting Us.** If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please click here to contact us.   
  
---
